enpass.io 2019-11-14

# Privacy Policy | Enpass

### Introduction

Your privacy is important to [Sinew Software Systems Pvt. Ltd.](https://sinew.io/) This statement describes the information practices for Sinew web sites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used.

### Enpass and browser extensions

Data entered in Enpass software by you either manually or through browser extensions is stays only with your computer. We do not store it on our servers. If you prefer to sync it with your other devices, your data is always travel through internet in encrypted form and never routed through our servers. Your master password is the only key for accessing your data. There are no back-doors.

### What Personal Information we collect

“Personal information” is data that reasonably can be used to identify or describe an individual. You do not need to provide us personal information to simply browse our site.

Sinew collects personal information when:

  * You request support for a Sinew product.
  * You register on our support forum.
  * You request information or materials (e.g., whitepapers or newsletters).
  * You participate in promotions, contests or giveaways.
  * You submit questions or comments to us.

Sinew also collects personal information from individuals (with their consent) at conventions, trade shows and expositions.

The types of personal information collected includes:

  * Your name.
  * Your e-mail address.

Sinew do not collect any other personal information from our products until & unless it is explicitly specified. Sinew may track the user’s behavior on our products using the third party analytics tools to make our products better to use.

### Use of Your personal information

Sinew collects and uses your personal information to communicate with you to improve its sites and products. These uses may include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use.

We may send certain mandatory service communications such as critical updates, information on technical service issues, and security announcements.

### Sharing of your personal information

Sinew will strictly not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others.

### Safeguarding your personal information

We recognize industry standards and employ security safeguards to protect information from unauthorized access and misuse. We request you to not send any sensitive information like Credit Card details or any other information on Contact us page.

### Enforcement

Sinew regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Statement. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this statement or Sinew’s treatment of personal information by contacting us. When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is Sinew’s policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this policy.

### Links to Other Sites

Our web sites often provide links to third-party web sites, such as those of our business partners, online advertisers and sellers. You should review their privacy policies to learn more about what, why, and how they collect and use personally identifiable information.

### Changes to the Sinew Privacy Statement

Sinew reserves the right to change this policy from time to time. If we do make changes, the revised Privacy Statement will be posted on this site.

This Privacy Statement was last amended on October 1, 2016.
